District of Columbia Library Association 039
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 3: Miscellaneous
  - DCLA Research, Undated (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Tree planting, 4/21/93 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - John Cole Research, Undated (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Draft of Text for "Capital Libraries and Librarians", Undated (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Copies of photographs considered for use and research letters, Undated (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Copies of items used in the exhibit and the book, Undated (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Early Libraries, Undated (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Early Handbook Covers for possible use in exhibit and look, Undated (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt, Undated (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Draft of Text for panels and book, Undated (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - LC photo research with Mary and Kathryn, 12/17/93 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Research Information, Undated (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Photos from National Geographic, Undated (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - DCLA Centennial Exhibit, Undated (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Statements of Work to the Humanities Council, Undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Dodge Hotel, Undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Panel showing who exhibit funders are, Undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Truax, Undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Victory Book Campaign (Docutext Copies), Undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Docutext Copy of Capitol Photograph, Undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - DCLA Logo Docutext Copy, Undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Docutext copies of photograph and other material from exhibit, Undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Material from exhibit (some not used), Undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Historic Correspondence and photographs, Undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Resolutions and brochures, Undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Spring Banquet, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Spring Banquet Photographs, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - ALA Washington Newsletter (not complete), 1977 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - ALA Washington Newsletter (not complete), 1978 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - ALA Washington Newsletter (not complete), 1979 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - ALA Washington Newsletter (not complete), 1980 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - ALA Washington Newsletter (not complete), 1985 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - ALA Washington Newsletters (not complete), 1986 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - ALA Washington Newsletter (not complete), 1987 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - ALA Washington Newsletter (not complete) 1988, Undated (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - WHCLIST, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Government Libraries Budgets - ALA Request for Action, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Addressing Ethnic and Cultural Diversity ALA Report, Undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - ALA Chapter Relations Meeting, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - ALA Council Minutes Midwinter, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - ALA Council Minutes Annual Meeting, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - ALA Council Minutes Midwinter, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Membership List, 2/4/91 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - DCLA Tee Shirt, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - "Centennial Times" (2 copies), Undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Proclamation from DC City Council, Undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Photo Album from New Member Reception, 10/28/93 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Panels from traveling exhibit for DCLA Centennial (see map case in Archives), Undated (Box 46, Folder 1)